<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<eml:eml xmlns:eml="https://eml.ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.2.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:schemaLocation="https://eml.ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.2.0 https://rs.gbif.org/schema/eml-gbif-profile/1.3/eml.xsd"
packageId="2ee19e1f-d4be-4d2e-96d4-50ebaf0a2efc"  system="http://gbif.org" scope="system"
xml:lang="en">
    <dataset>
        <title>GBIF Occurrence Download 0024588-250426092105405</title>
        <creator>
            <individualName>
                <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
            </individualName>
            <electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>
        </creator>
        <metadataProvider>
            <individualName>
                <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
            </individualName>
            <electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>
        </metadataProvider>
        <pubDate>
                2025-05-10
        </pubDate>
        <language>ENGLISH</language>
        <abstract>
            A dataset containing all occurrences available in GBIF matching the query:
{
  "TaxonKey" : [
    "is Trigona spinipes (Fabricius, 1793)"
  ]
}
The dataset includes records from the following constituent datasets. The full metadata for each constituent is also included in this archive:
27 records from Coleção Zoológica de Referência da Universidade Federal de Mato Grosso do Sul - Hymenoptera (ZUFMS-HYM)
1823 records from DSEC - Coleção Entomológica do Depto. de Sistemática e Ecologia
1042 records from Snow Entomological Museum Collection
29 records from Illinois Natural History Survey Insect Collection
149 records from Bee Biology and Systematics Laboratory
2 records from DZUP-Hymenoptera - Coleção Entomológica Pe. Jesus Santiago Moure (Hymenoptera)
1 records from Natural History Museum (London) Collection Specimens
1 records from The Albert J. Cook Arthropod Research Collection
3 records from Projeto Conexão Mata Atlântica - Monitoramento Ecossistêmico - Fauna e Flora - Rio de Janeiro - Campanha 06
1 records from ZUEC-HYM - Coleção de Hymenoptera do Museu de Zoologia da UNICAMP
12 records from Natural History Museum Rotterdam - Specimens
11 records from MCTP-Insetos - Coleção de Insetos
1 records from NMNH Extant Specimen Records (USNM, US)
884 records from DZUB - Coleção Entomológica da Universidade de Brasília
3225 records from MCP - Coleção de Abelhas
2 records from Projeto Conexão Mata Atlântica - Monitoramento Ecossistêmico - Fauna e Flora - Minas Gerais - Campanha 06
20 records from International Barcode of Life project (iBOL)
1 records from ZFMK Hymenoptera collection
2278 records from CEPANN - Coleção Entomológica Paulo Nogueira-Neto - IB/USP
1 records from Projeto Conexão Mata Atlântica - Monitoramento Ecossistêmico - Fauna e Flora - São Paulo - Campanha 02
1 records from Projeto Conexão Mata Atlântica - Monitoramento Ecossistêmico - Fauna e Flora - Minas Gerais - Campanha 01
1 records from ENGIE | Fauna's Rescue Program - Santo Agostinho Wind Farm, Rio Grande do Norte - Brazil
2 records from Coleção Entomológica Padre Jesus Santiago Moure (DZUP) - Hymenoptera
19 records from Museu Paraense Emilio Goeldi - Hymenoptera Collection
2 records from INSDC Sequences
1 records from Projeto Conexão Mata Atlântica - Monitoramento Ecossistêmico - Fauna e Flora - São Paulo - Campanha 06
15 records from Laboratório de Ecologia e Biogeografia de Insetos da Caatinga
2118 records from RPSP - Coleção Entomológica Prof. J.M.F. Camargo, FFCLRP/USP
2 records from Projeto Conexão Mata Atlântica - Monitoramento Ecossistêmico - Fauna e Flora - São Paulo - Campanha 01
4 records from Projeto Conexão Mata Atlântica - Monitoramento Ecossistêmico - Fauna e Flora - São Paulo - Campanha 04
2 records from NHMD Entomology Collection
368 records from hymenoptera
1689 records from iNaturalist Research-grade Observations
4033 records from Coleção Entomológica Moure e Costa

        </abstract>
        <contact>
            <individualName>
                <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
            </individualName>
            <electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>
        </contact>

    </dataset>

    <additionalMetadata>
        <metadata>
            <gbif>
                <dateStamp>2025-05-10T14:50:46Z</dateStamp>
                <citation identifier="0024588-250426092105405">GBIF Occurrence Download 0024588-250426092105405</citation>
                <physical>
                    <objectName>Darwin Core Archive</objectName>
                    <characterEncoding>UTF-8</characterEncoding>
                    <dataFormat>
                        <externallyDefinedFormat>
                            <formatName>Darwin Core Archive</formatName>
                        </externallyDefinedFormat>
                    </dataFormat>
                    <distribution>
                        <online>
                            <url function="download">https://api.gbif.org/v1/occurrence/download/request/0024588-250426092105405.zip</url>
                        </online>
                    </distribution>
                </physical>
            </gbif>
        </metadata>
    </additionalMetadata>
    </eml:eml>
